A Finding Aid to the Cranmer Art Group Records, circa 1980-2021, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Client Files, 1980-2021; Series 1; Archival Resource Key; 55.2 Linear feet Boxes 1-54, 75
  - Client Files, 2019, N-O, Archival Resource Key (Box 49, Folder 27)
  - Client Files, 2019, P, Archival Resource Key (Box 49, Folder 28)
  - Client Files, 2019, Pace Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 50, Folder 1-3)
  - Client Files, 2019, Phillips, Archival Resource Key (Box 50, Folder 4-6)
  - Client Files, 2019, R, Archival Resource Key (Box 50, Folder 7-8)
  - Client Files, 2019, S, Archival Resource Key (Box 50, Folder 9-10)
  - Client Files, 2019, Sotheby's, Archival Resource Key (Box 50, Folder 11-12)
  - Client Files, 2019, T, Archival Resource Key (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Client Files, 2019, UBS Art Collection, Archival Resource Key (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Client Files, 2019, V-Y, Archival Resource Key (Box 50, Folder 15-16)
  - Client Files, 2019, John Vlahakis (A. Perez Urriola), Archival Resource Key (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - 2020 Delivery and Stretcher Invoices, Archival Resource Key (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Client Files, 2020, A-B, Archival Resource Key (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Client Files, 2020, AGP Holdings One LLC (Ed Ruscha), Archival Resource Key (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Client Files, 2020, C, Archival Resource Key (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - Client Files, 2020, Christie's, Archival Resource Key (Box 50, Folder 22-23)
  - Client Files, 2020, Paula Cooper Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - Client Files, 2020, D, Archival Resource Key (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - Client Files, 2020, E-G, Archival Resource Key (Box 50, Folder 26-27)
  - Client Files, 2020, Gagosian Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 50, Folder 28-29)
  - Client Files, 2020, H, Archival Resource Key (Box 50, Folder 30-30)
  - Client Files, 2020, H, Archival Resource Key (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Client Files, 2020, I-K, Archival Resource Key (Box 51, Folder 2-3)
  - Client Files, 2020, L, Archival Resource Key (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Client Files, 2020, Lichtenstein Estate, Archival Resource Key (Box 51, Folder 5-6)
  - Client Files, 2020, Lisson Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 51, Folder 7-10)
  - Client Files, 2020, Museum Ludwig (Brice Marden), Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 flash drive. (Box 51, Folder 11-13)
  - Client Files, 2020, M, Archival Resource Key (Box 51, Folder 14-15)
  - Client Files, 2020, M. P. Daytona Capital LLC (Frank Stella), Archival Resource Key (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Client Files, 2020, N-P, Archival Resource Key (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Client Files, 2020, National Museum of Modern Art Tokyo (Peter Doig), Archival Resource Key (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Client Files, 2020, Pace Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 51, Folder 19-22)
  - Client Files, 2020, R, Archival Resource Key (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Client Files, 2020, Robert Rauschenberg Foundation, Archival Resource Key (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - Client Files, 2020, S, Archival Resource Key (Box 51, Folder 25-26)
  - Client Files, 2020, Sotheby's, Archival Resource Key (Box 51, Folder 27)
  - Client Files, 2020, Sotheby's, Archival Resource Key (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Client Files, 2020, T-W, Archival Resource Key (Box 52, Folder 2-3)
  - Client Files, 2020, Merrill Wagner, Archival Resource Key (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Client Files, 2020, Y-Z, Archival Resource Key (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Client Files, 2021, B, Archival Resource Key (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Client Files, 2021, Broadway 280 Park Fee, LLC (Ugo Rondinone), Archival Resource Key (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Client Files, 2021, C-G, Archival Resource Key (Box 52, Folder 8-9)
  - Client Files, 2021, Helen Frankenthaler Foundation, Archival Resource Key (Box 52, Folder 10-11)
  - Client Files, 2021, Anthony Grant Inc., Archival Resource Key (Box 52, Folder 12-13)
  - Client Files, 2021, H-K, Archival Resource Key (Box 52, Folder 14-15)
  - Client Files, 2021, L, Archival Resource Key (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Client Files, 2021, Roy Lichtenstein Foundation, Archival Resource Key (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Client Files, 2021, Frayda B. Lindemann (Agnes Martin), 2019-2021; Archival Resource Key (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Client Files, 2021, Lisson Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 52, Folder 19-20)
  - Client Files, 2021, M-R, Archival Resource Key (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - Client Files, 2021, Robert Rauschenberg Foundation, Archival Resource Key (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - Client Files, 2021, Phillips, Archival Resource Key (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - Client Files, 2021, S-W, Archival Resource Key (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - Client Files, Ellsworth Kelly (Artwork of 1949-1958 and unknown), 1999-2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 52, Folder 25-32)
  - Client Files, Ellsworth Kelly (Artwork of 1959-1965), 1997-2019; Archival Resource Key (Box 52, Folder 33)
  - Client Files, Ellsworth Kelly (Artwork of 1959-1965), 1997-2019; Archival Resource Key (Box 53, Folder 1-9)
  - Client Files, Ellsworth Kelly (Artwork of 1966-1979), 1996-2016; Archival Resource Key (Box 53, Folder 10-18)
  - Client Files, Ellsworth Kelly (Artwork of 1980-2012), 1997-2018; Archival Resource Key (Box 53, Folder 19-25)
  - Client Files, Ellsworth Kelly (General Projects), 2002-2018; Archival Resource Key (Box 53, Folder 26-27)
  - Client Files, Brice Marden (Artwork of 1961-1966), 1996-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 53, Folder 28-30)
  - Client Files, Brice Marden (Artwork of 1961-1966), 1996-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 54, Folder 1-3)
  - Client Files, Brice Marden (Artwork of 1967-1970), 1990-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 54, Folder 4-10)
  - Client Files, Brice Marden (Artwork of 1971-1974), 1989-2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 54, Folder 11-18)
  - Client Files, Brice Marden (Artwork of 1975-1985), 1989-2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 54, Folder 19-25)
  - Client Files, Brice Marden (Artwork of 1987-2010), 1993-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 54, Folder 26-30)
  - Client Files, Christopher Wool (Artwork Damaged in Hurricane Sandy), 2013-2019; Archival Resource Key (Box 54, Folder 31-33)
  - Client Files, Christopher Wool (Artwork Damaged in Hurricane Sandy), 2013-2019; Archival Resource Key (Box 75, Folder 1-5)
- Photographic Materials, circa 1980-2008; Series 2; Archival Resource Key; 19 Linear feet Boxes 55-74
  Photographs were removed from binders and are arranged alphabetically by artist. Slides are in sheets arranged by year, then alphabetically by artist.
  Photographs, snapshots, and digital photographs are primarily of artwork in the Cranmer conservation studio, dating from 1998 to 2003. Separate groups of photographs depict conservation staff and artwork by Donald Judd at Locksley Shea in 1999, and conservation staff with Frank Stella work, "Valparaiso Green," in the 1990s. Studio photographs are of conservation staff in the 1980s, 1990s, and 2000. Slides depict works of art and detail images of conservation concerns from 1988 to 2008. Researchers should note that most slides and photographs of Brice Marden and Ellsworth Kelly works are found in Series 1, Client Files.
  - Photographs, Artwork in Studio (Artists A), 1998-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Photographs, Artwork in Studio (Artists A-B), 1998-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Photographs, Artwork in Studio (Artists B), 1998-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 55, Folder 3-4)
  - Photographs, Artwork in Studio (Artists C), 1998-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Photographs, Artwork in Studio (Artists D), 1998-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Photographs, Artwork in Studio (Artists E-F), 1998-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Photographs, Artwork in Studio (Artists F-H), 1998-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Photographs, Artwork in Studio (Artists H), 1998-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Photographs, Artwork in Studio (Artists H-J), 1998-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Photographs, Artwork in Studio (Artists J-K), 1998-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Photographs, Artwork in Studio (Artists K-L), 1998-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Photographs, Artwork in Studio (Artists L), 1998-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Photographs, Artwork in Studio (Artists L-M), 1998-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Photographs, Artwork in Studio (Artists M), 1998-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 55, Folder 15-20)
  - Photographs, Artwork in Studio (Artists M-P), 1998-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Photographs, Artwork in Studio (Artists P), 1998-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Photographs, Artwork in Studio (Artists P-R), 1998-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Photographs, Artwork in Studio (Artists R), 1998-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 56, Folder 4-5)
  - Photographs, Artwork in Studio (Artists R-S), 1998-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Photographs, Artwork in Studio (Artists S), 1998-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 56, Folder 7-9)
  - Photographs, Artwork in Studio (Artists T-W), 1998-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Photographs, Artwork in Studio (Artists W-Y), 1998-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Photographs, Artwork in Studio (Various Artists), circa 1998-circa 2003; Archival Resource Key; 2 Electronic discs (CD) (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Photographs, Artwork in Studio, Donald Judd (Locksley Shea), 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 56, Folder 13-14)
  - Photographs, Artwork in Studio, Frank Stella, "Valparaiso Green", circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 56, Folder 15-16)
  - Photographs, Studio Pictures 1980s and 1990s, circa 1980-circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 56, Folder 17-19)
  - Photographs, Studio Pictures 2000, Archival Resource Key (Box 56, Folder 20-21)
  - Slides, 1988, B, Archival Resource Key (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - Slides, 1988, D-J, Archival Resource Key (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - Slides, 1988, K-O, Archival Resource Key (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - Slides, 1988, P-R, Archival Resource Key (Box 56, Folder 25)
  - Slides, 1988, Robert Rauschenberg, Archival Resource Key (Box 56, Folder 26)
  - Slides, 1988, R-S, Archival Resource Key (Box 56, Folder 27)
  - Slides, 1988, S, Archival Resource Key (Box 56, Folder 28)
  - Slides, 1988, T-W, Archival Resource Key (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Slides, 1988, W, Archival Resource Key (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Slides, 1989, A-B, Archival Resource Key (Box 57, Folder 3-4)
  - Slides, 1989, C-D, Archival Resource Key (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Slides, 1989, D-G, Archival Resource Key (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Slides, 1989, G-K, Archival Resource Key (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Slides, 1989, L-M, Archival Resource Key (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Slides, 1989, M, Archival Resource Key (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Slides, 1989, N-P, Archival Resource Key (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Slides, 1989, P-R, Archival Resource Key (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Slides, 1989, R, Archival Resource Key (Box 57, Folder 12-14)
  - Slides, 1989, S, Archival Resource Key (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Slides, 1989, T-W, Archival Resource Key (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Slides, 1989, W, Archival Resource Key (Box 57, Folder 17-20)
  - Slides, 1990, A-B, Archival Resource Key (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - Slides, 1990, B-C, Archival Resource Key (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - Slides, 1990, C, Archival Resource Key (Box 57, Folder 23-24)
  - Slides, 1990, D, Archival Resource Key (Box 57, Folder 25)
  - Slides, 1990, F-G, Archival Resource Key (Box 57, Folder 26)
  - Slides, 1990, H-I, Archival Resource Key (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Slides, 1990, I-K, Archival Resource Key (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Slides, 1990, L-M, Archival Resource Key (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Slides, 1990, M-N, Archival Resource Key (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Slides, 1990, P, Archival Resource Key (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Slides, 1990, R, Archival Resource Key (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Slides, 1990, S, Archival Resource Key (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Slides, 1990, T-W, Archival Resource Key (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Slides, 1990, W-Z, Archival Resource Key (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Slides, 1991, A-C, Archival Resource Key (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Slides, 1991, C-D, Archival Resource Key (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Slides, 1991, D-J, Archival Resource Key (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Slides, 1991, K-M, Archival Resource Key (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Slides, 1991, M, Archival Resource Key (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Slides, 1991, O-P, Archival Resource Key (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Slides, 1991, R-S, Archival Resource Key (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Slides, 1991, S-W, Archival Resource Key (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Slides, 1991, Y, Archival Resource Key (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - Slides, 1992, A-B, Archival Resource Key (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - Slides, 1992, B, Archival Resource Key (Box 58, Folder 20-22)
  - Slides, 1992, C-D, Archival Resource Key (Box 58, Folder 23)
  - Slides, 1992, D-G, Archival Resource Key (Box 58, Folder 24)
  - Slides, 1992, H, Archival Resource Key (Box 58, Folder 25)
  - Slides, 1992, J-K, Archival Resource Key (Box 58, Folder 26)
  - Slides, 1992, L, Archival Resource Key (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Slides, 1992, M, Archival Resource Key (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Slides, 1992, M-N, Archival Resource Key (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Slides, 1992, N-P, Archival Resource Key (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Slides, 1992, P-R, Archival Resource Key (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Slides, 1992, R-S, Archival Resource Key (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Slides, 1992, S-T, Archival Resource Key (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Slides, 1992, T-W, Archival Resource Key (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Slides, 1992, W, Archival Resource Key (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Slides, 1992, W-Y, Archival Resource Key (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Slides, 1993, A, Archival Resource Key (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Slides, 1993, A-B, Archival Resource Key (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Slides, 1993, B-F, Archival Resource Key (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Slides, 1993, F-H, Archival Resource Key (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Slides, 1993, H-K, Archival Resource Key (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Slides, 1993, K-M, Archival Resource Key (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Slides, 1993, M-O, Archival Resource Key (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Slides, 1993, O-R, Archival Resource Key (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Slides, 1993, R, Archival Resource Key (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - Slides, 1993, R-S, Archival Resource Key (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - Slides, 1993, S-V, Archival Resource Key (Box 59, Folder 21)
  - Slides, 1993, W-Z, Archival Resource Key (Box 59, Folder 22)
  - Slides, 1994, A-D, Archival Resource Key (Box 59, Folder 23)
  - Slides, 1994, D-G, Archival Resource Key (Box 59, Folder 24)
  - Slides, 1994, G-H, Archival Resource Key (Box 59, Folder 25)
  - Slides, 1994, J-K, Archival Resource Key (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Slides, 1994, L-M, Archival Resource Key (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Slides, 1994, M, Archival Resource Key (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Slides, 1994, N-O, Archival Resource Key (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Slides, 1994, P-S, Archival Resource Key (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Slides, 1994, S-V, Archival Resource Key (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Slides, 1994, V-W, Archival Resource Key (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Slides, 1995, A-B, Archival Resource Key (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Slides, 1995, B-C, Archival Resource Key (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Slides, 1995, D-H, Archival Resource Key (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Slides, 1995, J-M, Archival Resource Key (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Slides, 1995, M, Archival Resource Key (Box 60, Folder 12-14)
  - Slides, 1995, N-P, Archival Resource Key (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Slides, 1995, R, Archival Resource Key (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Slides, 1995, S, Archival Resource Key (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Slides, 1995, T, Archival Resource Key (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - Slides, 1995, W, Archival Resource Key (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - Slides, 1996, A, Archival Resource Key (Box 60, Folder 20-22)
  - Slides, 1996, B, Archival Resource Key (Box 60, Folder 23-24)
  - Slides, 1996, C-D, Archival Resource Key (Box 60, Folder 25)
  - Slides, 1996, D, Archival Resource Key (Box 60, Folder 26-27)
  - Slides, 1996, D-G, Archival Resource Key (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Slides, 1996, G, Archival Resource Key (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Slides, 1996, H, Archival Resource Key (Box 61, Folder 3-4)
  - Slides, 1996, J-K, Archival Resource Key (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Slides, 1996, K, Archival Resource Key (Box 61, Folder 6-9)
  - Slides, 1996, L, Archival Resource Key (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Slides, 1996, L-M, Archival Resource Key (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Slides, 1996, M, Archival Resource Key (Box 61, Folder 12-13)
  - Slides, 1996, N, Archival Resource Key (Box 61, Folder 14-15)
  - Slides, 1996, P-R, Archival Resource Key (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Slides, 1996, R, Archival Resource Key (Box 61, Folder 17-18)
  - Slides, 1996, S, Archival Resource Key (Box 61, Folder 19-20)
  - Slides, 1996, T-V, Archival Resource Key (Box 61, Folder 21)
  - Slides, 1996, V-W, Archival Resource Key (Box 61, Folder 22)
  - Slides, 1996, W, Archival Resource Key (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - Slides, 1996, W, Archival Resource Key (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Slides, 1996, W-Y, Archival Resource Key (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Slides, 1997, A, Archival Resource Key (Box 62, Folder 3-5)
  - Slides, 1997, B, Archival Resource Key (Box 62, Folder 6-8)
  - Slides, 1997, D, Archival Resource Key (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Slides, 1997, E-F, Archival Resource Key (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Slides, 1997, F-G, Archival Resource Key (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Slides, 1997, G-H, Archival Resource Key (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Slides, 1997, H, Archival Resource Key (Box 62, Folder 13-14)
  - Slides, 1997, H-J, Archival Resource Key (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Slides, 1997, J-K, Archival Resource Key (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Slides, 1997, K, Archival Resource Key (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Slides, 1997, K-M, Archival Resource Key (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - Slides, 1997, M, Archival Resource Key (Box 62, Folder 19-21)
  - Slides, 1997, N, Archival Resource Key (Box 62, Folder 22)
  - Slides, 1997, O-P, Archival Resource Key (Box 62, Folder 23)
  - Slides, 1997, P-R, Archival Resource Key (Box 62, Folder 24)
  - Slides, 1997, R, Archival Resource Key (Box 62, Folder 25)
  - Slides, 1997, R-S, Archival Resource Key (Box 62, Folder 26)
  - Slides, 1997, S, Archival Resource Key (Box 63, Folder 1-2)
  - Slides, 1997, T, Archival Resource Key (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Slides, 1997, V, Archival Resource Key (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Slides, 1997, W-Y, Archival Resource Key (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Slides, 1998, A, Archival Resource Key (Box 63, Folder 6-9)
  - Slides, 1998, A-B, Archival Resource Key (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Slides, 1998, B, Archival Resource Key (Box 63, Folder 11-12)
  - Slides, 1998, C, Archival Resource Key (Box 63, Folder 13-14)
  - Slides, 1998, D, Archival Resource Key (Box 63, Folder 15-16)
  - Slides, 1998, Willem de Kooning, Archival Resource Key (Box 63, Folder 17-18)
  - Slides, 1998, D-F, Archival Resource Key (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - Slides, 1998, F, Archival Resource Key (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - Slides, 1998, F-G, Archival Resource Key (Box 63, Folder 21)
  - Slides, 1998, H, Archival Resource Key (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - Slides, 1998, H-J, Archival Resource Key (Box 63, Folder 23)
  - Slides, 1998, J-K, Archival Resource Key (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - Slides, 1998, K, Archival Resource Key (Box 64, Folder 1-2)
  - Slides, 1998, L, Archival Resource Key (Box 64, Folder 3-5)
  - Slides, 1998, M, Archival Resource Key (Box 64, Folder 6-8)
  - Slides, 1998, N-O, Archival Resource Key (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Slides, 1998, O-P, Archival Resource Key (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Slides, 1998, R, Archival Resource Key (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Slides, 1998, R-S, Archival Resource Key (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Slides, 1998, S, Archival Resource Key (Box 64, Folder 13-15)
  - Slides, 1998, T-V, Archival Resource Key (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Slides, 1998, W, Archival Resource Key (Box 64, Folder 17-19)
  - Slides, 1999, A, Archival Resource Key (Box 64, Folder 20-22)
  - Slides, 1999, B, Archival Resource Key (Box 64, Folder 23-24)
  - Slides, 1999, C-D, Archival Resource Key (Box 64, Folder 25)
  - Slides, 1999, D, Archival Resource Key (Box 64, Folder 26)
  - Slides, 1999, D, Archival Resource Key (Box 65, Folder 1-2)
  - Slides, 1999, E-F, Archival Resource Key (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Slides, 1999, F, Archival Resource Key (Box 65, Folder 4-5)
  - Slides, 1999, G-H, Archival Resource Key (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Slides, 1999, H-K, Archival Resource Key (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Slides, 1999, K-L, Archival Resource Key (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Slides, 1999, M, Archival Resource Key (Box 65, Folder 9-11)
  - Slides, 1999, N-O, Archival Resource Key (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Slides, 1999, P-R, Archival Resource Key (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Slides, 1999, R, Archival Resource Key (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Slides, 1999, S, Archival Resource Key (Box 65, Folder 15-17)
  - Slides, 1999, T, Archival Resource Key (Box 65, Folder 18-19)
  - Slides, 1999, W, Archival Resource Key (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - Slides, 1999, W-Z, Archival Resource Key (Box 65, Folder 21)
  - Slides, 2000, A, Archival Resource Key (Box 65, Folder 22-23)
  - Slides, 2000, B, Archival Resource Key (Box 65, Folder 24)
  - Slides, 2000, B-C, Archival Resource Key (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Slides, 2000, D, Archival Resource Key (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Slides, 2000, F, Archival Resource Key (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Slides, 2000, G, Archival Resource Key (Box 66, Folder 4-5)
  - Slides, 2000, H, Archival Resource Key (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Slides, 2000, J-K, Archival Resource Key (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Slides, 2000, K-L, Archival Resource Key (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Slides, 2000, L-M, Archival Resource Key (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Slides, 2000, M, Archival Resource Key (Box 66, Folder 10-13)
  - Slides, 2000, N-P, Archival Resource Key (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - Slides, 2000, P-Q, Archival Resource Key (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - Slides, 2000, R, Archival Resource Key (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - Slides, 2000, R-S, Archival Resource Key (Box 66, Folder 17)
  - Slides, 2000, S, Archival Resource Key (Box 66, Folder 18-19)
  - Slides, 2000, S-T, Archival Resource Key (Box 66, Folder 20)
  - Slides, 2000, T-V, Archival Resource Key (Box 66, Folder 21)
  - Slides, 2000, W-Z, Archival Resource Key (Box 66, Folder 22)
  - Slides, 2001, A, Archival Resource Key (Box 66, Folder 23-24)
  - Slides, 2001, A, Archival Resource Key (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Slides, 2001, B, Archival Resource Key (Box 67, Folder 2-3)
  - Slides, 2001, C, Archival Resource Key (Box 67, Folder 4-5)
  - Slides, 2001, F, Archival Resource Key (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Slides, 2001, G-H, Archival Resource Key (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Slides, 2001, H, Archival Resource Key (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Slides, 2001, H-J, Archival Resource Key (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Slides, 2001, K, Archival Resource Key (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Slides, 2001, K-L, Archival Resource Key (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Slides, 2001, M, Archival Resource Key (Box 67, Folder 12-16)
  - Slides, 2001, N, Archival Resource Key (Box 67, Folder 17)
  - Slides, 2001, O-P, Archival Resource Key (Box 67, Folder 18)
  - Slides, 2001, P, Archival Resource Key (Box 67, Folder 19)
  - Slides, 2001, R, Archival Resource Key (Box 67, Folder 20-25)
  - Slides, 2001, S, Archival Resource Key (Box 68, Folder 1-3)
  - Slides, 2001, T, Archival Resource Key (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Slides, 2001, U-V, Archival Resource Key (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Slides, 2001, W, Archival Resource Key (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Slides, 2001, W-Y, Archival Resource Key (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Slides, 2002, A, Archival Resource Key (Box 68, Folder 8-9)
  - Slides, 2002, B, Archival Resource Key (Box 68, Folder 10-11)
  - Slides, 2002, C, Archival Resource Key (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - Slides, 2002, C-D, Archival Resource Key (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - Slides, 2002, D-F, Archival Resource Key (Box 68, Folder 14)